I was in North Carolina. It's my first job, 15. They were in a red Camaro talking, a white couple.
And while they were talking, they weren't paying attention. So I was handing them their drinks.
So, you know, they talking like this. When they turned and realized that it was me handing them
their drinks, they threw them back at me. I just want to understand what you're telling me.
I just want to tap in and understand what you're telling me. I want to tab in and understand what
you're telling me. You're saying that white people in Greensboro, North Carolina? I was in Eden,
in my hometown. You were in Eden, North Carolina, and white people in a Camaro were mad that a
black woman was serving them drinks? In the 90s. That was not my first time being called
the N-word, but... The reason why that's partially just bonkers to me is because like, if there's
one place that white people have never seemed to have a problem with us being, it's in servitude.
So it's like, what? They didn't want me touching their cups.